菲比   你能帮我挑个订婚戒指给摩妮卡吗
Pheebs, can you help me pick an engagement ring for Monica?
我没法决定   好难挑啊
I can't figure this out. It's so hard.
我要选第凡内切割法的  还是公主方切割法的还是
Should I get her a Tiffany cut, or a princess cut or a--
噢噢   被纸切割法
Ow! Paper out!
你跟其他人说了吗
Now, have you told anyone else?
没有  我没告诉其他人  我不想让摩妮卡发现
No, I don't want to tell anybody else because I don't want Monica to find out.
可你告诉我了
You told me.
因为我信任你   你是我最好的朋友之一
Well, that's because I trust you, and we're best friends...
还有我正在看戒指广告的时候   你进来了
...and you walked in on me while I was looking at ring brochures.
下次我不敲门进来的话
Yeah well, once again, not knocking pays off.
我只希望你不要刚好在蹲马桶就好了  我希望也是
I only wish you hadn't been on the toilet. Me too.
嘿   嘿
Hey. Hey.
钱德  要不要去喝咖啡  好啊  走吧
So Chandler, wanna go to the coffeehouse? Oh, all right.
好极了  我们正想找你们一块去
Oh, perfect. We were just gonna see if you wanted to go.
不了  我们去另外一家
Oh, well, we don't, because we got the other place.
真没礼貌
How rude.
抱歉  你想咬一口吗
Oh, I'm sorry. You want a bite?
老友记  第六季  第23集  订婚戒指
Friends  S06E23  The One With The Ring
主演: 珍妮佛·安妮斯顿
主演: 寇妮·考克斯
主演: 丽莎·库卓
主演: 麦特·勒布兰
主演: 马修·派瑞
主演: 大卫·修蒙
（中央咖啡厅）
你和保罗交往得怎么样
So how are things going with Paul?
很好啊
Good. Huh.
只不过   他不太爱说话
Although, you know, he's a private guy. Mm-hm.
真想让他稍微敞开点心胸   好分享他的感受
You know, I wish I could get him to open up a bit. Share some feelings.
这太容易了   把他当成一罐打不开的泡菜
That's easy. You just have to think of him as a jar of pickles that won't open.
你是说
So, what are you saying?
我应该把他泡进热水里   然后把他的头往桌子上撞
I should run him under hot water and bang his head against a table?
不是  那是严刑逼供
No, that's what you do when you want to get the truth out of someone.
嗨  嗨
Hi. Hi.
你好吗   看我的
How are you? Watch this.
嘿  保罗  嘿   菲比
Hey, Paul. Hi, Phoebe.
你最近好吗
So how are things going with you?
没说的
Can't complain.
嘿   嘿
Hey! Hi.
嗨  罗斯  我也很高兴见到你
Great to-Ross, good to see you too.
我很好   拜  保重
Good. Bye. You take care.
菲比   你们在搞什么鬼   钱德还放我们鸽子
Hey, Pheebs, what was the deal with you and Chandler blowing us off before?
很奇怪  对吧
Ah, that was so weird, huh?
菲比   为什么要这么做
Phoebe, why did you do it?
不是我   是钱德
I didn't do it. It was Chandler.
他  他在生你的气
He's-He's mad at you.
什么   为什么  拜托   你明知故问
What? Why? Oh, please. I think you know why.
我想不起来
I can't think of anything.
罗斯  你是古生物学家  再往下挖深一点
Come on, Ross. You're a paleontologist. Dig a little deeper.
等等   是不是因为两个星期前   乔伊和我没找他
Wait a minute, is it because Joey and I didn't invite him to that Knicks game...
去看纽约尼克斯队的球赛
...a couple weeks ago?
你觉得他会为这种事生气吗
Do you think that's something that he'd be mad at you for?
应该会  那好  我也是这么想
I guess it could. Well, then I think that's it.
如果他生气了  他为什么不说呢
Well, if he's angry, he really shouldn't just cover it up.
我希望他能告诉我
I wish he'd just tell me the truth.
那你应该抓着他的头
Oh, if that's what you want...
泡进热水里  再把他的头往桌子上撞
...then you really should run him under hot water and bang his head against the table.
亲爱的   我在中国花园订了位   你好了吗
Honey, I made a reservation at China Garden. Is that okay?
可以啊   太棒了
Yeah, that's great.
先等等   给我说说说   你今天好不好
But first, wait, talk to me, talk to me. Tell me about your day.
蛮好的
It was fine.
好吧
0Kay.
嘿   你在想什么  你此刻在想什么
Hey, what are you thinking? What are you thinking right now?
我在想你穿这条裙子真漂亮
I'm thinking that you are looking really fine in that dress.
太好了  保罗  但是
Yeah, that's great, Paul. But, you know...
我想知道  哇  好结实
I want to know what-Wow, those are really great.
我想知道
I just want to know...
在这坚强平静的外表下面到底隐藏着什么
...what is behind this strong, silent exterior?
俗语说静水深流
You know, they say that still waters run deep...
我想在你的心中畅游
...and I want to swim in yours.
你是说做爱
Are you talking about having sex?
不  保罗
No, PauL
我一点也不了解你
I don't know anything about you.
比如你的童年   跟我聊聊你小时候的事吧
You know, like your childhood. Tell me about your childhood.
很普通
Normal.
好吧  那青春期呢  如何  那是一段痛苦的时光
Okay, well, then how about puberty? Come on. That's always a painful time.
你的朋友请你参加聚会
You know, your friends invite you to a slumber party...
趁你睡着   把你的手放进热水里
...and stick your hand in warm water...
让你尿在睡袋里
...while you're sleeping so that you pee in your sleeping bag.
我没碰过那种事
No, that never happened to me.
那是你走运   没碰上那个贱人莎朗麦杰斯基
Well, you're lucky you never met that bitch, Sharon Majeski.
总之
Anyway...
你有后悔过吗
The rest of your life, you know. Any regrets?
没有
No.
好吧   保罗  我要求得不多
All right, Paul. I'm not asking for a lot here.
你就告诉我点什么   随便什么都行
Okay? Just give me something. Anything.
好吧  好
okay. okay
我6岁那年
When I was 6 years old... Mm-hm.
想要一辆大脚踏车
...I wanted a Big Wheel.
父母却送我一只  塑料小鸡
And instead, my parents got me this little...
骑着到处跳的那种
...plastic chicken that you hop around on.
太难为情了  小朋友都取笑我
It was embarrassing. Kids made fun of me.
那一年  真够难过的
That was a pretty tough year.
太好了  你看吧
That's great. See? Heh.
我觉得我更了解你了   谢谢
I already feel like I know you a little better. Thank you.
好  我们去吃饭吧   走吧
Okay, come on. Now we can go eat. Let's go.
我好惨
It was horrible.
他们都叫我 "小鸡孩"
They called me "Chicken Boy."
五年级我跟别人打架   其实也不算真打了
In fifth grade, I got in a fight. Well, it wasn't really a fight.
理查达伦一拳打在我鼻子上
Richard Danville bit me on the nose.
我摔倒了  这里留了个小伤疤  你看嘛
I fell down, still have a little scar right here. You can see it.
有  我看见了
Yeah, yeah. I see the scar.
保罗  你听我说  你能分享这些感受真是太好了
Listen, Paul, I think this is really great that, you know, you've shared your feelings.
真的很棒
It's really... It's beautiful.
但是你刚才说我们去吃什么
But, urn, what do you say we go share some food?
我现在吃不下
No, I couldn't eat now.
说什么啊   你最爱吃宫保鸡丁了
What are you talking about? You love their Kung Pao chicken.
鸡
Chicken?
鸡弟弟  天哪  对不起  我不是故意的
Chicken Boy! I'm sorry. I didn't mean to do that.
逛了几百家首饰店   一无所获
Well, this is the nine millionth ring store we've been to...
还是找不到完美的戒指
...and I can't find the perfect ring.
难看  难看  难看
Ugly ring, ugly ring, ugly ring...
漂亮  精品
It's a beautiful selection.
要不然   你不要送戒指
Okay, so maybe you don't get her a ring.
送点不一样的
Maybe you do something different, you know?
例如订婚手镯   或是订婚皇冠
Maybe you get her an engagement bracelet. Or an engagement tiara.
或者  一把订婚独立战争毛瑟枪
Ooh! An engagement Revolutionary War musket.
真高兴选你来帮忙
You know, I'm so glad I picked you to help me with this.
想像一下你单膝跪地
Can't you imagine getting down on one knee...
向她献上这把漂亮的武器
...and handing her this gorgeous piece of weaponry?
我看   还是送戒指好了
Yeah, I'm gonna stick with the ring.
这只好漂亮   我喜欢这只
Oh, this one's nice. I like it this one.
先生  大哥  我可以看这枚戒指吗
Sir? Kind sir, can I see this one?
等等   你找我来就是因为
Wait a minute. This is the reason you brought me, okay?
我会砍价  所以接下来交给我处理
I know how to haggle. So let me handle this from here on out.
有什么需要吗
Can I help you?
有  我想看那枚戒指   要么什么都不看  随便
Yes, I would like to see that ring, please. Or not. Whatever.
这是一只20年代的戒指
This ring is from the 1920s.
上面有1点5克拉钻石   两侧各镶有蓝宝石
It's a one-and-a-half karat diamond with sapphires on either side.
先生  你能不能
Sir, could I ask you to, um...?
拿出这只戒指向我求婚
Could you hold out that ring and ask me to marry you?
好啊   好
Okay. Okay.
你愿意嫁给我吗
Will you marry me?
天哪  就是它了  就选这个
Oh, my God, that's it. That's the ring.
多少钱   钱德   让我来
How much is it? Chandler, I will handle this.
多少钱
How much is it?
8千6百元块美元
Eight thousand six hundred.
我们出10块
We will give you $10.
你到底想不想买啊  想  想
Are you interested in this ring? Yes. Yes.
但我只能出8千块
But I can only pay $8000.
好  8千可以  我们坚持只付10块钱
Okay. I can let it go for 8. We stand firm at $10.
您用什么付帐   刷信用卡
How would you like to pay? Uh, credit card.
喔   糟了  我的卡在乔伊那边了
Oh, no. No, no, but I lent my credit card to Joey.
没事  我回去拿   你守住戒指  好的
Okay, I'll go get it. You guard the ring. Okay.
刚才的事很抱歉啊
Listen, I'm sorry about before.
你们这里有10块钱的东西吗
Do you have anything here for $10?
有啊   我有两张崭新的
Uh, yes. I have these two rather beautiful...
5元钞票
...five-dollar bills.
我出1块钱跟你买
I'll give you $1 for them.
嘿  记得钱德和菲比昨天把我们甩了吗
Hey, remember how Chandler and Phoebe blew us off yesterday?
不记得
No.
记得吗  你当时在吃披萨   对啊
Remember, you were eating pizza? Yeah.
很明显  钱德在生气
Well, apparently Chandler's angry at us...
就为我们两星期前   没帮他买纽约尼克斯队的球票
...for not getting him a ticket to that Knicks game a couple weeks ago.
我们为什么要帮他买票
What, we were supposed to just get him a ticket?
那家伙老是揩我们的油   就是啊
That guy is always mooching off of us. Yeah.
但不管怎么样   我想我们该做点什么
Anyway, I still think we should try to patch things up, you know?
也许我们可以给他搞张尼克斯队比赛的票和他一起去看
Like, maybe we could get him tickets to another Knicks game and invite him.
好主意   而且他的信用卡也在我这里
Wow, that's a great idea. And I still have his credit card.
您的帐单
Here you go.
嘿  嘿  我有卡  拿去吧
Hey, hey. I got this one. Here you go.
我跟你说  有时候我真搞不懂钱德
You know, I gotta tell you, sometimes I just don't get Chandler.
我们一直背着你出去玩
You know, me and him do stuff all the time without you...
你也不会生气
...and you don't get all upset.
一直   一直
All the time? All the time.
我的天哪   我的天哪
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
还在哭   跟小女生一样
Still crying? Like a little girl.
我知道   我知道都是我不好
I know, I know, I know. This is all my fault.
是我要他敞开心胸的
I wanted him to open up.
但是我不知道我会放出一头
But God, I didn't know that I was gonna unleash...
哭哭啼啼又黏人的怪物
...this weepy, clingy, moist monster.
我只知道有两种方法可以让男人闭嘴
You know, I only know of two sure-fire ways to shut a man up.
其中一种是性爱
And one of them is sex.
另外一个是呢   不知道
What's the other? I Don't know.
我从来不需要用到另一种
I never had to use the other one.
我只是说  如果作爱就没时间讲话
I'm just saying, you know, if we're having sex, he's not talking.
没错  话多的是你
Ah, that's right. You're the talker.
不管怎么说  是个好主意  对
Anyway, uh, great idea. Yeah.
我得去趟商店   我答应去帮他买纸巾
Um, I gotta go to the store. I told him that I would buy him some more tissues.
我们这里有  不  你们没有
Uh, we have some here. No, you don't.
好  我还想试试这顶王冠
Okay. Um, I'd also like to try on the tiara.
太好了
Oh, yeah. Okay.
你觉得怎么样   太花了
Wow, what do you think? Too much?
有点点
A tad.
好吧  把皇冠放回去
Then take the tiara back...
再让我试试那把枪
...and let me hold the musket again.
少了点什么
Something's missing.
好   把我朋友挑的戒指拿给我看看
Let me see the ring that my friend picked out.
那枚20年代的钻戒呢
Where's the 1920s princess-cut ring?
刚刚卖给那位先生了
I just sold it to that gentleman.
完蛋了
Oh, my God!
等等   别走
Wait, no!
放我出去   快点
Let me out! Now!
瑞秋
Rachel?
不是
No.
保罗  你好吗   还好
How are you, Paul? Okay.
钱德
Chandler...
你爸抱过你吗   没有  他抱过你吗
...did your dad ever hug you? No. Did he hug you?
没有  没有
No. No.
我父亲从来没拥抱过我
It's just that my dad never did.
我好想念我爸
I miss my dad.
你可以去赌城   看我爸亲别人的爸爸
Well, you can see my dad in Vegas kissing other dads.
嘿   钱德   怎样
Hey, Chandler? Yeah?
你能不能
Would you...?
你能不能抱抱我
Would you hug me?
我现在有点忙  保罗  我爸以前都这么说
I'm a little busy here, Paul. That's exactly what my dad used to say.
好啦  就一下下  来吧  快点
Okay. A quick one. Come on, hug it out.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
行了吧
There you go.
好了
0Kay.
再多5秒钟   够了
Five more seconds-Okay.
乔伊  什么   嘿
Joey! What? Hey, what--?
嗨   保罗  是吧
Hi. Paul, is it?
你拿了我的信用卡  是  在我的
Do you have my credit card? Yeah. It's in my...
我的口袋里
In my pocket.
后面的口袋  后袋  幸好
My back pocket. Back pocket. Thank God.
听着  我买了今晚尼克斯队的票  我不能去
Listen, I got tickets to the Knicks tonight. I can't go.
去啦   会很好玩的
Come on, it'll be fun.
我  你  罗斯  也许还有保罗
Me, you, Ross and... Paul, probably.
钱德   我找到了最完美的戒指
Chandler, I found the perfect ring.
真不错   但我还是想买之前挑重的那款
Oh, that's pretty nice, but I'm gonna go with the one I picked first.
天哪  钱德  你挑的那只戒指不在了  没了
Oh, wake up, Chandler. The one you picked is gone. It's over.
什么
What?
对不起  被人买走了  我想拦住他  却被他们关进监狱里
Some guy bought it. I'm sorry. I tried to stop him but they put me in jail.
把你关进监狱里   就是两道门之间的小监狱
They put you in jail? The little jail between the doors!
菲比  我要你看着那只戒指  我知道  对不起
Phoebe, I asked you to guard the ring. I know. I'm sorry.
你看  这只更漂亮   摩妮卡莫不会看到其他戒指的
But, you know, this ring is better. And Monica never even saw the other ring.
是啊  但是他用那只戒指向我求婚时  我起了鸡皮疙瘩
Yeah. But when he proposed to me with the ring, I got goose bumps.
也许是因为那个男人  是因为那枚戒指
Maybe it was the guy. It was the ring.
嘿  他听到票的事兴奋吗  不  他回绝了
Hey, so was he excited about the tickets? No. He blew us off.
什么  真的
What? I know.
真不敢相信
I can't believe it.
告诉你
Can I tell you something?
我现在真的有点生他的气
I'm a little mad at him now.
告诉你
Can I tell you something?
我也是
Me too.
他生气不告诉我们
You know what? He didn't want to talk to us about being angry?
那好吧  我们也什么都不要告诉他
Well, maybe we don't talk to him at all.
把他打入冷宫   没错
Freeze him out. That's right.
我喜欢  给他好看
I like it. Ah? We'll show him.
从今以后  就是乔伊与罗斯  最佳拍档
From now on, it's gonna be Joey and Ross, best friends.
我们将是新的乔伊与钱德
Okay, we're gonna be the new Joey and Chandler. Ha, ha.
嗨  我回来了
Hi, I'm back.
我把想说的话都写下来了
Hey! I have so much more to tell you. I've written it all down.
真好
Oh, that's great.
其实  这个
No, actually, that's...
真是太好了  真的好棒
That's great. That's really great.
说真的  写字  写东西  会燃起
You know, I gotta tell you, writing, all that writing, it gets me, uh...
燃起我的欲火
It gets me kind of hot.
等等  你听这个
Wait, wait. Listen to this:
你知道我小时候想当什么吗
Know what I wanted to be when I was that age?
情圣
A lover?
冲浪运动员   是吗  冲浪运动员
A surfer. Oh, yeah. A surfer?
我想与海浪为伍  停一停
I wanted to be one with the waves-Honey, hold on real quick.
等一下  让我坐得更舒服一点
Hold on a second. Let me just get a little more comfortable here.
等一下
Wait, now wait a second,
我这样是不是太暴露了  不会
This isn't too revealing, is it? No.
当年那个小家伙呢
Whatever happened to that little dude?
充满了梦想
So full of dreams.
我不在乎那个什么小家伙
I don't care about the little dude.
我没办法   我听不下去了
I can't. I cannot listen to any more of this.
只有心理医师才想听这些话
Y'know, the only person who'd listen to this is a mental health professional.
因为他们听这个每1小时赚1百元
And that's only because they get paid $100 an hour.
你知道我听到现在可以赚多少
Do you know how much money I could've made listening to you?
2000块钱
Two thousand dollars.
你知道我什么时候算出来的   就在你说话的时候
And you know when I figured that out? While you were talking.
你居然想让我闷死吗  14个小时前
I can't believe you're trying to stifle me, when just 14 hours ago...
我们刚刚谈到我妈就是想这么对我的
...we figured out that that's exactly what my mother was trying to do to me.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不是有意的  我不是想把你闷死
I don't mean... I didn't mean to stifle you.
我只是没办法控制自己
This is all just a little overwhelming.
瑞秋
Oh, Rachel.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
我不是故意的
I didn't mean to overwhelm you.
只不过情绪一发泄
It's just that when those gates open...
就容易一发不可收拾
...it's hard to close them.
不过现在没事了  真的
But they are closed now. Believe me.
我很高兴  你跟我分享这些事
I'm so glad. I'm so glad you shared.
也很高兴你说完了
And I'm glad that you're done.
那我们要不要
So, what do you say we, um...
我求之不得
I'd really like that. Mm-hm.
真是太棒了
That was so good.
嘿   我居然听了你的话
Hey. I can't believe you talked me into...
买了这只造型怪异的廉价戒指
...buying this stupid gumball-machine-looking ring.
它才不廉价呢   看它多漂亮啊
It's not a stupid gumball-machine-looking ring. It's a beautiful ring.
才不漂亮呢
No, it's not.
另外一枚戒指
When I looked at the other ring...
我能看见拿给摩妮卡时的表情
...I could see Monica's face when I gave it to her...
还能看到她点头答应
...and I could see her saying yes.
看看这只戒指   怎么看它都是一只戒指
When I look at this ring, all I see is a ring.
只有近看  才能看到我的眼睛
Unless I look at it really closely, and then I can see my own eye.
这是我这辈子要做的最重要的一件事
Look, this is the most important thing I'm gonna do in my life.
我希望做的完美无缺
I want to make sure it's perfect.
好   那我们或许还有办法把那只戒指要回来
Okay. There may be a way that we could get the other ring back.
我偷听到那人告诉珠宝店  他准备求婚的地方
Because I heard the guy tell the jeweler where he was gonna propose.
或许我们可以说服他交换或怎么样
So maybe we could get him to trade rings or something.
我做不到
I can't do that.
你总不能给她那只廉价的戒指吧
Well, you certainly can't give her that stupid gumball ring.
他在那
There he is.
还好  他还没求婚   那个女的没有戴戒指
Okay, and he hasn't proposed yet. She has no ring on her finger.
你真行   下次我们应该一起来破案
Wow, you're good. After this, we should solve crimes.
没错  去请他过来
Yeah. Okay. Go get him.
好吧
Oh, okay.
抱歉   先生  请您过来一下  有您的电话
Excuse me, sir. Could you come with me, please? You have a phone call.
是谁   是你的办公室打来的
Who is it? It is your office.
你知道是谁吗  约翰
Do you know who at my office? John.
约翰啊  太好了
Oh, John. Great.
他来了   你好
There he is. Hi. Hi. Okay.
是这样  珠宝店搞错了
Okay, there was a mix-up at the jewelry store.
你打算用来求婚的戒指是我预订的
The ring you're about to propose with was supposed to be held for me.
所以我想把它换回来
So I'm gonna need to have that back.
不过作为交换   我愿意拿这只更漂亮更值钱的戒指和你交换
But in exchange, I'm willing to trade you this beautiful, more expensive ring.
哇  要是我就换了
Wow, I would trade.
的确很漂亮   但是我就想用这只求婚  失陪了
It is beautiful, but I'm gonna use this one. Now, if you'll excuse me.
不  不  这位是我的未婚妻   她就是要这枚戒指
No, no. See, this is my fiancée, and her heart was set on that ring.
你不会想伤她的心吧
You don't want to break her heart now, do you?
对啊   你想伤一位垂死女人的心吗
Yeah. Do you want to break a dying woman's heart?
你要死了
You're dying?
她快死了
Yeah, she's dying...
很明显  她快咳死了
...of a cough, apparently.
对  这是我临死前的愿望  如果我不能戴着这只戒指安息
It's my dying wish to have that ring. See, if I'm not buried with that ring...
我就会变成孤魂野鬼游荡在阴间
...then my spirit will wander the netherworld--
好了  够了  亲爱的
Okay, that's enough, honey.
我不知道
Oh, I don't know.
让我看看戒指   当然  看吧
Let me see the ring. Great. Okay, here.
好吧  谢谢  谢谢  谢谢
All right, I'll do it. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
你会嫁给一个很棒的男人
And you are about to marry a wonderful man.
嘿   我要娶一个快死的女人
Hey, I'm marrying a dead woman.
兄弟们
Guys?
我有大事要宣布
I got something important to tell you.
兄弟们
Guys.
Guys?
兄弟们
我要跟摩妮卡求婚了
I'm gonna ask Monica to marry me.
我们应该让他从冷宫走出来了
I think we gotta end the freeze-out.
等等   你是来真的
Wait a minute. Is this for real?
对啊   戒指都在这里
Yeah. Check out the ring.
天哪
Oh, my God.
这么说你们是认真的
So you two are really serious?
对  非常认真
Yeah, pretty much.
你们  你们要结婚了  我是说
You're gonna get married? I mean...
我们要成为连襟了  过来
We're gonna be brothers-in-law. Come here!
我们又可以当朋友了  嘿
And we're gonna be friends again. Hey.
什么
What?
过去的事就别提了  好吧
Water under the bridge. Forget it! Okay.
我本来想等到正式公开的那天  可我太兴奋了还是忍不住要告诉你们
I was gonna wait till it was official, you know, but I got so excited I just had to tell you guys...
因为你们是我最好的朋友
...because you're my best friends.
我真想哭   别再哭了
I think I'm gonna cry. Oh. No more crying.
拜托   我刚甩掉一个爱哭宝宝  小心我也甩了你
Please, I just dumped one cry baby. I'll dump you too.
我要跟摩妮卡求婚
I'm gonna ask Monica to marry me.
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
钱德  你们一定会很幸福的
Oh, Chandler. You guys are gonna be so happy.
我知道   可纸巾都死哪去了
I know. Where's all the tissues?
看这是戒指
Check out the ring.
真好   至少有1点5克拉
Oh, nice. One-and-a-half karat, easy.
嘿  嘿  菲比
Hey. Hey, Pheebs.
钱德要跟摩妮卡求婚了
Chandler's gonna ask Monica to marry him.
我知道  是我陪他去挑的戒指
I know. I helped pick out the ring.
你先告诉她
You told her before you told us?
她进来的时候正好看到我在看戒指广告
Well, she walked in while I was looking at ring brochures.
你们能谅解的   对吧
You can understand that, right?
兄弟们
Guys?